univideo2u.com 2012-05-04

# UniVideo2u™ | Watch & Earn

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the UniVideo2u™ website at www.univideo2u.com ("Website"). On some pages, you can register for an account, make requests, and register to receive information. The types of personal information collected at these pages may include: 

  * Name
  * State of Residence
  * Zip Code
  * Gender
  * Email address
  * Month and Year of Birth
  * City
  * Social Security number

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you are working to add people to your critaria, you will need to submit the recipient's email address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information that we might collect are: 

  * Name
  * Email address

We use the information that you provide about yourself to better tailor advertisements that you are served from our Advertiser community. For example, if you said that you are interested in technology, we might use your information to select you as the recipient for technology advertisements. We may also use this information to contact you directly for various purposes, including if you win a prize and/or to obtain Rewards in accordance with Website policy. We do not directly share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete a reward or other payment.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers to provide targeted advertisements for your review. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

We use the information you provide about someone else only to send them information about registering with   
UniVideo2u™ at your request. We do not share this information with outside parties.

We use return email addresses to answer the email that we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information that we collect online.

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by accessing your   
UniVideo2u Profile. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please write to us at:

1 Sentral Level 16,   
Jalan Stesen Sentral 5  
L Sentral  
Kuala Lumpur 50470  
Malaysia

…or send an email to [privacy@univideo2u.com](mailto:privacy@univideo2u.com).
